Andre Volpato



0416 922 722



https://www.linkedin.com/in/andre-volpato-

O Cabarita, NSW 2137

EDUCATION

[2018 -]

Bachelor of **Engineering** (Mechanical),

University of New South Wales [Expected Completion - Dec 2021]

[2010 - 2017]

St. Patricks College, Strathfield 92.80 ATAR Awards:

- St. Gabriel's School Award for Social Justice (2017)
- Mathematics Prize (2017)
- McGlade Scholarship (2016)

PROFESSIONAL **MEMBERSHIPS**

Student Member of Engineers Australia

KEY ATTRIBUTES

- Attentive to detail
- Work well in team environment
- Problem solving
- Time management

CAREER SUMMARY

A passionate final year mechanical engineering student engineer at UNSW who is keen to launch into an engineering internship/cadetship or graduate role for 2022 and turn study into practice, gain valuable hands-on experience and mentorship while discovering what I love to do.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Administrator

De Martin & Gasparini

(DEC 2017 - PRESENT)

De Martin & Gasparini provides specialist concrete pumping and placement services for commercial and high-rise developments across the industrial, residential and utility sectors.

Key Responsibilities

- Conducted drawing change assessments for 7+ large commercial & residential projects across Sydney
- Estimate volumes of concrete from structural and architectural drawings
- Complete variation prices to provide to clients
- Created Excel spreadsheet in conjunction with project manager for cost vs. budget analysis
- Collate quality assurance documentation

Support Worker

Hireup

(MAR 2021 - PRESENT)

Crew Member

McDonald's Westfield Burwood

(NOV 2014 – OCT 2016)

SKILLS

- Microsoft office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint)
- Adobe Acrobat
- Solidworks
- Autodesk Fusion 360
- ANSYS (Finite Element Analysis and CFX)
- MATLAB

Languages:

- English (Native)
- Italian (Advanced)